<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cycling on Matt Kharrl</title>
    <link>https://matt.kharrl.com/tags/cycling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cycling on Matt Kharrl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 14:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matt.kharrl.com/tags/cycling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Race Recap: BWR California</title>
      <link>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/recap-bwr-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/recap-bwr-california/</guid>
      <description>Date Race Duration Type Location Category Result May 1, 2022 BWR California 75 miles Gravel Race California, CA Overall 143 / 611 I was aware of the rising gravel scene but didn&amp;rsquo;t lean in until I binge-watched the &amp;ldquo;Impossible Route&amp;rdquo; YouTube documentary series created by Vegan Cyclist. The whole idea of gravel riding (dare I say the spirit of gravel) seemed to reignite the adventurous side of cycling which first drew me in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race Recap: Tour de Mesa</title>
      <link>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/recap-tour-de-mesa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 13:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/recap-tour-de-mesa/</guid>
      <description>Date Race Duration Type Location Category Result Apr 1, 2022 El Tour de Mesa 42 miles Road Race Mesa, AZ Ovarall 98 / 965 Tour de Mesa in 2022 was a 42-mile mass-start road race event involving over 1,000 riders. It featured two laps through the east Phoenix desert and a fair bit of climbing.
Going into the event, I thought I would just put in a decent effort and focus on PRing the main climb (Usery Pass) on one of the laps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race Recap: South Mountain Bike Classic</title>
      <link>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/recap-somo-classic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/recap-somo-classic/</guid>
      <description>Date Race Duration Type Location Category Result Mar 26, 2022 South Mountain Bike Classic 30 minutes Circuit Race Phoenix, AZ CAT 5 5 / 11 South Mountain Bike Classic was technically classified as a circuit race but it felt pretty similar to a crit with a lap length of about one mile. This course was much more technical than Avondale Crit and featured much more elevation (&amp;gt;100 feet per mile).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race Recap: Avondale Crit</title>
      <link>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/recap-avondale-crit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/recap-avondale-crit/</guid>
      <description>Date Race Duration Type Location Category Result Mar 20, 2022 Avondale Crit 30 minutes Criterium Race Avondale, AZ CAT 5 4 / 14 I started racing in March 2022, which I soon learned is already halfway through the spring racing season here in Arizona. I knew little about bike racing (tactical or logistical) and had no idea what my strengths or weaknesses might be.
My first-ever race was a CAT 5 crit, which I was warned would be chaotic and dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The riding before the racing</title>
      <link>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/riding-before-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matt.kharrl.com/blog/riding-before-racing/</guid>
      <description>Bikes have been part of my life in some capacity for most of my life. Walmart bikes as a kid, street BMX bikes as a teenager, fixed-gear bikes in college, and road bikes as a young adult. This relationship was casual and adventurous, focusing more on getting lost with a camera and less on training zones.
After moving from San Franciso to Phoenix, my morning rides went from &amp;ldquo;climbing coastal mountains and crossing the golden gate bridge&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;riding from flat suburbs to flat farmland.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
